Amazon offers a variety of self-service advertising solutions.
Understanding your business goals will help you select the right advertising products for your goals
and better analyze the performance of your ad campaigns.
Depending on your business goals, you may want to use different advertising solutions
in your advertising campaigns.
In this video, you'll learn how you can use Amazon ad solutions
to help meet your business objectives.
The customer's journey is rarely linear.
Shoppers may move across different stages such as awareness, consideration, and purchase
as they navigate the Amazon store.
Amazon ad solutions can help you meet objectives
that support shoppers at each stage of the journey, such as helping discover your brand,
browse your products, and drive purchases.
Depending on your goals, your campaign strategy
may change.
For example, if you're looking to help customers discover your brand, you may want to
create a sponsored display campaign with lifestyle audiences to reach customers that may be interested
in your products.
To help drive purchases with customers who are familiar with your brand,
you may want to use sponsored display with views remarketing audiences to remind customers of
products they may have previously considered.
Let's talk through some more examples of how you can use
Amazon ad solutions to help achieve different business goals.
Accent athletics have been selling
sportswear accessories in the Amazon store for two years.
They've established a customer base,
but now are looking at expanding their business with more products and a wider audience.
To do so,
Accent athletics is looking at Amazon ad solutions that can help them meet their business goals
and
objectives.
Their first goal is to reach more customers and build awareness around their brand
and products.
To achieve this goal, they ran a sponsored brands campaign that can help customers
discover their brand and products with creative ads that appear in relevant Amazon shopping results.
Similarly, Accent athletics can also run a sponsored display campaign to help build brand awareness
by promoting their products or a memorable brand story to customers while they shop or engage with
content they love.
To gauge success, they look at how many impressions their ads drove indicating
that the ads are displaying to their target audience.
Their next business goal is to increase
traffic to their product detail pages, which could help more customers consider their brand and
products.
They run a sponsored brands campaign that links to their own Amazon store using their best-selling
products to help engage customers as they browse.
They review their product detail page views to
see if these ads are effective at meeting this goal.
Lastly, Accent athletics is looking to
increase sales to grow their business.
To achieve this goal, they use a sponsored products campaign
to help boost sales of individual products.
With sponsored products ads, a single click takes
customers directly to the product detail page to make a purchase.
With their focus on growing
audience and driving traffic, they want to ensure that they are also helping drive purchases with
the audience.
Accent athletics can also consider a sponsored display campaign to help increase sales
as it could help them easily discover, reach, and engage the right customers in the most relevant
context across their shopping journey.
Similar to Accent athletics, you can use different Amazon
ad solutions to help meet your business goals.
Amazon ads has billions of shopping, streaming,
and browsing signals to help connect your brand with the right customers at the right time in
brand-safe placements.
Ready to get started?
Visit ads.
amazon.
com.